LOW HUAN CHI

+6018-9011 388 | lowhuanchi@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/lowhuanchi/ |

SUMMARY

Fresh Graduate from Universiti Malaya (UM) with various leadership experiences in cocurricular activities. Driven and enthusiastic team player empowered with strong adaptability, creativity, and communication skills. Strong passion in pursuing a sales and marketing career.

EDUCATION

Universiti Malaya (UM)

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Bachelor of Business Administration (Marketing Major) CGPA: 3.88, First Class Honor, JPA Scholarship

October 2020 – January 2024

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing Intern

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Nestlé Products Sdn Bhd – Nestlé Ice Cream

July 2023 – January 2024

- Supported in Brand Marketing activities execution including stakeholder management through brainstorming ideas, revising proposals, and managing content delivered from creative, media and KOLs agencies, as well as relationship building and reviewed up to 40 multi-racial KOLs content (Phei Yong, Dizzy, Kuan Family, MK K-Clique)
- Market Visit to different trade outlets and collaborate with cross-functional team to collect customer's feedback and improve sales strategies on Ice Cream.
- Supported in Below the Line (BTL) operational marketing including product and sample arrangements for advertisement production shoot, and POSM creatives reviews.
- Assisted in MILO Kaw Ice Cream, Nestlé BOBA Pint, KITKAT Ice Cream, and Nestlé Blue Tub marketing campaign including product ideation, sales strategy planning, support the main advertisement production and photoshoot, assist 1 month Klang Valley roving activation, review KOLs and content publisher postings.
- Co-leaded the Nestlé Ice Cream Contest 2024 and assisted in key visual & POSM development.
- Managed social media (Facebook, Instagram) with 1 million followers and developed up to 60 social contents including Instagram Reels that has 24,000 views.

Human Resource & Finance Intern

Instahome Sdn Bhd

August 2021 – October 2021

- Assisted Human Resources in recruitment, 10 new employees onboarding and 3 employees offboarding arrangement, employee compensation and benefits management.
- Arranged 100 interviews and screened up to 5 candidates includes 2 successful hires.
- Supported the Finance team in 50 employee claims and sales commissions checking.

EXTRA-CURICCULAR ACTIVITIES

Executive of Creative and Arts Session 2021/2022

University of Malaya Business Club (UMBC)

June 2021 – *June* 2022

- Selected as one of the 13 Board of Directors in overseeing and managing UMBC operations.
- Designed up to 30 materials using Adobe Photoshop for UMBC projects and advise 3 annual events of more than 60 committee members each regarding publishing matters.

• Collaborated with 2 clubs in creating up to 10 promotional materials for FBE Professional and Career Day, and 5 corporates (GTI Media, Nestle, Shopee, KPMG, and Arthur D. Little)

Senior Executive of Multimedia and Technical Department

Malaysian Business Student Summit (MBSS)

November 2021 – *March* 2022

- Guided a team of 10 members to create promotional video shooting and editing using Adobe Premiere Pro for the event that consists of 80 participants from local and private universities.
- Worked as a primary facilitator in leading the team up to 10 participants.

Apprentice of Boost Life Project Track

ICMS EMBARK

October 2022

- Worked with 2 teammates to solve the Boost App's stickiness issue within 2 weeks.
- Presented the Boost Track and Receipt feature in visually concise pitch deck to Axiata.

Associate Consultant

UYC Consulting Project (UYCCP)

August 2022 – October 2022

- Identified client's key insights and performed inventory management research and analysis.
- Provided support to lead consultant's initiative in meeting up with client and work with other consultants in identifying the client's needs.
- Compiled and presented the recommended solution in the visually effective deck to the client.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Oueens Guide Award
- Champion of UMAC Malaysian Accounting Students Convention (MASC), 2022
- 1st Runner Up of GTI Media Digital M100 Challenge 5.0, 2021
- 2nd Runner Up of Overall Business Simulation of ULDP under Axiata Young Talent Program (AYTP)
- 2nd Runner Up of CEO Challenge of ULDP (AYTP)
- 2nd Runner Up of FABS BIGWORLD UUM, 2021
- Top 5 Finalists of The Malaysian Project Case4Impact, 2022
- Top 5 Finalists of The Awakened Solutions: ESUM Case Study Competition, 2022
- Top 7 Finalists of Alibaba Global E-commerce Challenge, 2023
- Top 8 Finalists of INTEC PACE Young CEO Challenge, 2022

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Technical Skills: Adobe Photoshop Skill, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premier Pro, Video Editing Skill, Microsoft Excel

Soft Skills: Adaptability, Communication, Time Management, Detail-oriented, Problem Solving

Certifications: L'Oréal MT Simulation (Career Hackers), The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (Google Digital Garage), Microsoft Advertising Certified Professional, Introduction to Data Analysis using Microsoft Excel (Coursera)

Languages: English, Mandarin, Malay